One hundred thousand.
Don't worry about that,
this money is enough to rent the room.
He is a long-time friend,
a daddy's boy,
he doesn't lack money.
Come on, let's eat first,
I'm hungry.
Shen Xi.
You're really good at acting.
A daddy's boy,
rent a room...
It's not like that.
Shen Xi.
You disgust me.
You disgust me with this ballet,
you make our dreams disgusting.
Everything we did together,
you make him absolutely disgusting.
It's not like that,
I'm not who you think.
Believe me.
We can go ask Feng Shu,
we can go ask Gao Yuhai.
What am I supposed to ask him?
It was they who forced me to do it.
What should I ask him?
Water.
It's this water bottle.
Fengshu made me drink a bottle of water
and then I don't remember anything anymore.
It's true, believe me!
I believe you.
Shenxi.
It's entirely my fault.
I should never have done this ballet,
I should never have become a director.
I should never have had dreams.
It's all my fault,
It's all my fault.
It's my fault, it's my fault.
Pardon, Shenxi.
Don't do that.
Pardon.
It's all my fault.
Non.
Yanfei! Yanfei!
Cleared !
Sale.
Shen Xi.
It's over between us.
Inspector Li,
Thank you for listening to me for so long.
I have a few more words
that I want to leave to Song Yanfei.
I think I won't have
probably no longer the opportunity to tell him in private.
Could you pass them on to him for me?
Yanfei,
when you hear this recording,
we will already be separated by death.
Merci.
Thank you for making my dream come true.
You made me the true heroine of this ballet.
I think that
me, without a mask on stage,
I had to glow, didn't I?
And I, who endured so long before falling,
I certainly had to become the center
of the whole room, even of the whole city.
Song Yanfei,
This is my revenge against you.
You are the real murderer.
Am I right?
You don't need to contradict me.
Song Yanfei,
If I hadn't met you back then,
I would never have put on this ballet.
I would not have participated
in this dance competition for money.
And even less sacrificed
my honor and my body for victory.
That said,
You know
why did I kill myself on stage?
This is my revenge against you.
I want to make you suffer for the rest of your life.
I want
that with each performance of this ballet,
you remember
that I died at the end of this play.
It's my fault.
It was me who killed her.
It was me who killed Shen Xi.
Xingchen.
It's my fault.
I was too impulsive that day.
I was too impulsive when I got the photos.
I should have consoled her, right?
I should have consoled her.
It's my fault.
Is there anything else?
SO ?
Was it satisfying?
Song Yanfei,
have I ruined this work?
Did I ruin your happiness?
But that said,
you really don't have the right to speak
because I sleep with others for money.
Not even mentioning the fact that it was for you,
even if it was for myself,
how are you better than me?
You too, for the money,
you abandoned me
and you got together with Gao Yayan, right?
It's the hospital that doesn't care about charity.
Does that make sense?
This Shen Xi recording
is only for you.
We're not going to make Gao Yayan listen to it.
As for you,
what you choose to say
or not to say, it's you who see.
Non.
I can say everything.
Is
recognize,
is
I'm really a bastard,
it's for the money
and for the musical I approached Gao Yayan.
It's true.
But now I really find
that we are more compatible.
Kindred spirits.
So I'll bring in Gao Yayan,
We still have a few things to check.
How are you ?
Okay, call her.
Jiang,
bring in Gao Yayan.
Welcome, Chief Li.
Got it.
Where is the restroom ?
When leaving, turn right.
Miss Gao, what's going on?
Are you thinking about this car again?
In accordance with the regulations,
we have already dealt with it.
I remember,
I called you before proceeding.
Well, this way, please.
In fact, I know everything.
You know ?
When I was little,
my father controlled every aspect of my life.
I just knew he was busy every day with 45509.
He didn't really let me see my maternal grandparents either.
Until,
because of this dance story,
I decide once and for all to free myself from its influence.
It was only afterwards that I understood little by little
that everything that was around me
was nothing other than
the character he had created for himself.
I have never been a gentleman.
Brother, Brother, attends!
I'll announce it, okay?
I'm looking for my father,
I need you to announce it?
It's because our president is too busy,
he has a thousand things to manage.
I'm afraid you'll disturb him.
I'll announce it, okay?
Disturb him?
On the contrary, he will be delighted, push yourself!
You weren't supposed to be super busy
with a thousand affairs to manage? Where are you?
Let's wait in the rest room,
I'll get Director Gao for you, okay?
Go ahead, look for it.
I'm waiting here.
Who is it ?
Why all this noise?
Yanyan, how come you are here?
Quoi,
I can't come?
I'm disturbing your little affairs, right?
I was resting a little.
What is this one for?
What is it for, tell me?
She dares to stop me?
She can't stop me anyway.
I just wanted to see
what Mr. Director Gao does every day, so busy
to manage a thousand affairs.
All right.
Truly impressive, Director Gao.
Thank you for your work.
Come out first.
I'll settle accounts with you later.
And you too,
get out quickly.
Director Gao,
SO
don't forget what you promised me.
Shark.
Fasten your seat belt.
He swore in front of my maternal grandparents
that he would never remarry in his life.
But when my mother died,
he was barely in his thirties.
Even if he had really decided
to remarry honestly,
I wouldn't have said anything.
But him?
On the one hand,
he was acting,
and on the other, he did the worst things.
He even brought this woman in front of my mother.
It's simply
a desecration.
He didn't deserve the love my mother gave him.
Your father
and the candidates of the dance competition,
the abuses he committed,
were you aware?
You mean
that it's not just Shen Xi?
We re-interviewed Li Fang from the dance competition
as well as Professor Mu, the choreographer.
We re-interviewed them all.
They all recognized
that your father, Gao Yuhai,
had sex
with at least three or four people.
Every Saturday, he pretended to go and keep my mother company in the old house.
But one day, when I went to look for him,
he wasn't there.
Last Saturday, where were you?
Where I am every Saturday,
you don't know that?
You're lying.
So last Saturday,
did you go to the old house?
I went there.
I searched every corner of the old house.
But where were you?
Did you go to the wine cellar?
The wine cellar he was talking about
is located in a corner of the courtyard of the old house.
My mother's ashes are kept there.
and all the decor of their old wedding.
To verify what he was saying,
I installed
a micro-camera in the wine cellar.
I installed this camera
only to check
if he really was going
see my mother every week.
I didn't expect
to accidentally record all his filth.
Shark.
There was a little traffic.
What's wrong with you, Yanyan?
Nothing, let's order.
I just watched a series,
it was touching.
Didn't you wait for me so we could watch it together?
What do you want to eat?
What we eat is not important.
the important thing is that I want to drink today.
Drink ?
Why do you want to drink?
You don't always ask me
what is happening in my family?
Today I'm going to tell you everything.
All right.
So where do I start?
Let's start with
a tricycle.
This tricycle,
my grandfather contacted lots of people to find him.
I had just bought it for my father.
Before that day,
I had never told anyone about it.
The story between my father and my mother.
But seeing these disgusting images in surveillance,
his image as a father
completely fell apart for me.
After that,
the contents of the camera,
I didn't want to watch it anymore.
And if I had to describe in two words
the one I call my father,
it would be:
garbage.
And then this Feng Shu,
he is in cahoots with Gao Yuhai.
What kind of man he is,
Gao Yuhai knows this very well.
But he still forced me to marry him.
If it wasn't because of Shen Xi's matter,
I would probably already be engaged to him by now.
Even a fierce tiger does not devour its cubs.
How can we
push your own daughter
in the mouth of the wolf?
Exactly,
Shen Xi left a recording for the two of you.
Let's listen to it together.
I lost my honor,
I lost love.
What sense is there in me still living?
This bottle of medicine...
I've been preparing for a long time,
but I never had the courage to swallow it.
That day,
I was on the roof,
and I danced the main role one last time
that Song Yanfei had written for me, with all my soul.
I told myself that I no longer had any regrets.
But just as I was about to swallow this bottle,
I suddenly realized
that I still had one important thing left to accomplish.
Tuer Gao Yuhai —
this scum who hid behind a mask of virtue.
I knew
that he went to the old house every Saturday.
That day happened to fall on a Saturday.
I decided
to take action that day.
Main actors (listed in order of last name traits)
Li Xingchen — Yu Xiaotong
Gao Yayan — Zhang Keying
Yan Yongmei — Fang Ming (Fang Xingyi)
Feng Shu — Liu Yakun
Bai Xiaosi — Liu Xiaolong (Liu Xubai)
Bai Sha — Li Xintong
Bai Jiuzhou — Qin Peng
Weng Wei — Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Police Technician — Kang Hairu
Forensic pathologist — Cheng Gong
Petit Bai Xiaosi — Zhang Weilun
Jeune Song Yanfei
Li Fang — Xu Yue
Lead singer — Xu Weina
Wu Dalong — Sui Dalong
Guests / Extras
Policiers — Yang Menglin, Wang Yiguo
Father of Xiao Ze — He Meng
Mere de Li Xingchen — Dong Dong
Zhao Wenjuan — Li Ziying
Camarades — Xiao Ba, Niu Dali
Yao Sha
Secrétaire — Qian Duoduo
Woman — Sun Meili
Fillette — Yingying, Huang Mingfei
Actionnaires — Huang Xinyang, Wang Wentao
Secrétaire de Gao Yuhai — Dudu
Chauffeur en fuite — Liu Haohan
Chauffeurs — Wang Yiguo, Liang Hui
Liu Ran
Serveurs — Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Chauffeur Lao Zhao — Wei
Locksmith
Mother of Xiao Ze — Pei Xiao
Technicien Xiao Zhang — Li Chen
Secrétaire — Qian Duoduo
Injured — Xu Ganggang
Teacher — Ai Li
Mère de Yan — Zhang Minghui
Médecin — Wang Keming
Neighbor — Wu Meiling
Clients du barbecue — Cheng Gong, Qiu Yaqiong
Guo Xinye
Homme en noir — Zhu Yiqi
Doublure de Li Xingchen — Tang Li
Song Yucheng — Liang Zhengchao
Police officer — Wu Lihua
Yan Yongmei — Li Tianjun
Execution doctor — Sister Geng
Actor — Hu Zexuan
Presenter
Receptionist — Wang Yanmin
Restaurant owner
Réceptionniste Xiao Yu — Ren Jiefei
Generic
Hai Ziqing
Guo Guo
Counselor — Bai Di
General distributor — Hu Kaichen
Production team
Hu Kaichen
Producers: Sui Sanlong, Li Xin
Zhang Shining
Executive producers: Peng Xia, Kang Hairu
Scenario planning: Zhang Wanlu
Production Director: Liu Zhilong
On-set production: Hu Huazheng
Coordination: Liu Xinyu
Régisseurs: Xu Ganggang, Zhao Menglin
Yang Qunbao
Cuisine
Chef: Yin Baoxin
Vegetable preparation: Hu Xiuxia
Driver team
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Wang Ji
Zhang Kai, Liang Hui
Niu Yuwang, Wang Yi
Zhang Haiping, Cao Yongjie
Production team
Director: Yue Shunming
Co-director: Xu Yue
Executive director: Sui Chenggong
Assistant directors: Tang Yuye, Li Gaoyang
Actor coordination: Kang Hairu
Mechanic
Wu Yingjie
Sound team
Sound director: Zhang Kai
Assistants son: Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Sets and props team
Artistic Director: Zhao Daqian
Executive artistic direction
Deputy Art Director: Wang Tianyi
Head of props
Accessories manager: Sun Donghua
Main set supervisor: Hou Yonghao
Assistant stage supervisor: Li Yao
Chang Ang
Image team
Director of photography: Li Yixu
First camera assistant: Yao Yonglei
Camera Assistant A: Li Xinghan
First camera assistant B
Camera Assistant B: Cao Xing
Drone framer: Zhan Yuchen
Making-of : Li Chen
Lighting team
Lighting assistant: Zhang Xiaoguang
Head of costumes and makeup: Ma Yi
Head of hair and makeup on set: Li Zixu
Hair and makeup set: Liu Lu, Guo Xinye
Costumes plateau: Zhang Tingting, Qiu Yaqiong
Beijing Zhehen Kele Culture Media Co., Ltd
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Media manager
Project coordination: Zhao Zihan
Post-production
Coordination post-production : Zhang Xiaoman
Dong Jiayi
Calibration Wizard
Credits: Gao Dong
Subtitle production: Su Li
Ambient sound editing: Zhang Xinyu
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture Communication Co., Ltd
Production supervisor: Gao Dong
Compositeurs: Gao Dong, Wu Yingjie
Beijing Landuo Music
Directeur musical: Xiao Zhuang
Production musicale: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Daifu
Guitare: Liu Zining
Female voice: Ma Qianran
Music mixing: Zhao Yi
Mixage chansons: Zhao Yi, Zheng Suyang
Recording studio: Beijing Landuo Studio
Songs
Yue Shunming
Compositeur Xiao Zhuang
Producteur Xiao Zhuang
“The Spring Song”
Performed by Zhang Keying
Child voice Zhang Maolin
Paroles de Yue Shunming
Paroles de Bai Yuxiang
Gao Jingman
Paroles de Gao Jingman
“Half a beat slower”
Performed by Xu Yue
Composer Xu
Wang Weijia
Paroles de Bai Yuxiang
Arrangement Zhao
Producteur Xiao Zhuang
Compositeur Xiao Zhuang
Shiyan Municipal Committee Propaganda Department
Fangxian Luling Wang Liquor Industry Co., Ltd
Hubei Zhiyuxuan Agricultural Technology Co., Ltd
Shiyan Dongfeng Historical Archives Museum
École Dongfang Yuanzhi in the district of Maojian, Shiyan
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate Co., Ltd (Résidence Longcheng)
Management Co., Ltd
Maojian District Yangguang Dance Art Training School, Shiyan
Dépanneur Meiyijia, 88 rue du Parc, district of Zhangwan, Shiyan
Exclusive social media platform
Weibo
Main partner media
Beijing Suishi Brothers Film and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd
Sichuan Jiaodian Film Industry Co., Ltd
Co-producing companies
Sichuan Lengjing Chuangjie Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd
Songyuan Senshengda Trading Company
Qinghe (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd